Hurry up, dammit!
[MIKASA] I'm trying!
It's them. You've got
to get out of here!
Eren! Just take
Mikasa and run! Now!
I want to, more than anything!
[EREN] But first I
need you on your feet!
Sweetie, listen to me.
My legs have been crushed.
Even if you could get me
out of here, I can't run.
There's no time.
Whatever! I can carry you!
Will you just shut up and listen
to me for once in your life?
[CARLA] One thing I'm asking
you! One thing!
[CARLA] Mikasa, make him!
[MIKASA] I can't.
You want all
three of us to die?
Hannes!
Take the children and
get them out of here!
Come on, Carla; that's
not our only option.
Hey, I'm a trained soldier.
My skill set is killin'
Titans and saving lives!
[CARLA] No, wait!
Don't do this! Please!
[thinking] Nothing fancy.
Just take it down.
Get all three of
'em out of harm's way.
Make good on the debt you owe!
[gasp]
[EREN] No! What are you doing?
Put me down, you bastard!
Thank you, Hannes.
[EREN] Wait! No!
[EREN] We can't
just leave her! Mom!
I love you! You hear me?
[CARLA] Stay alive!
♪
[crying]
Don't leave me.
♪
Stop it! Nooooo!
[NARRATOR] And just like
that. Everything changed.
[NARRATOR] At that terrible
moment, in our hearts, we knew.
[NARRATOR] Home was
a pen. Humanity, cattle.
[NARRATOR] Shiganshina
crumbles. Prayers are useless.
[NARRATOR] Tears are absurd.
Death agonies are nothing.
[NARRATOR] When total
ruin is your reality,
[NARRATOR] all that's left
of any value is revenge.